Friend, if you want to know the status of your application
, then for that you will have to
click on the home button on the Delhi Jal Board website and then you will
reach the information section.
You have to click on Track Application Status.
Which gives you ARN number.  If
you have a new connection like this was our
process for new connection.
You have to click on New Connection.  Then
you get the ARN number here.
You have to fill that ER number here.  You have to
fill the captcha.  Then after this you have to click on the search button.
As soon as you click on the search button,
you will see the number of steps here to know
what is the current status of your application?
If your final submission is done here, then a message
of successfully submitted appears here
and a message of can number generation also
comes and
a can number gets generated on the mobile number you have given.
If this application
is rejected then 'Application Rejected' appears here
and its reason is also displayed.  If
you have been assigned a side verification officer,
you will also see a remark here stating "Side Verification Done."